Maxwell Muhanda

Software Engineer

ajaybullec@gmail.com







About

My name is Maxwell Muhanda, a full-stack web developer currently based in Kenya. My Passion for software is 100% driven by ideas i dream of and my want to make them a reality. I strive to deliver high quality code alongside a great user experience in every product I build.

I also do Digital marketing, particularly web SEO and social media marketing all inspired with current industry tools and the ability to create engagements over through technology.

Outside of programming, I enjoy travelling, video games and watching Football. I treasure the feeling of making wonderful memories.

Projects

Instruct 7

An uber for legal services

Portfolio website 7

my personal website

Vue Todo O

Simple Todo app with vue3 & firebase



Pong Africa [↗]

Telecommunication company website

Random Image O

Vue random image generator

★ 0

Work Experience

Pong Agencies Limited Digital Marketing & Software Development

Executive

Oct 2021 - Sep 2022 | Nairobi Kenya

- Build and execute digital marketing campaigns to support Pong Agencies Marketing
- Built company website and online store
- Optimize SEO & analytics for company platforms
- Manage & generate content on social media platforms

Instruct Backend Developer

Apr 2022 - Present | Remote

Backend & DevOps engineer

- Developed the rest API backend for Instruct
- Cloud deployment and management
- SEO & Digital Marketing for platform

Office of the Attorney General Industrial Attachment

May 2021 - Aug 2021 | Nairobi, Kenya

Provided technical support on HR department

Stacks

Frontend Typescript, Javascript, Vue, Tailwind

Backend Django, Flask, MySQL, Nginx, Docker, Kubernates

Marketing SEO, Analytics, SEM, Social Media

DevOps Firebase, Azure, Linode

Languages Python, JavaScript, PHP, SQL

Education

Marketing, Bachelor of Commerce, St Paul's University

Aug 2018 - Nov 2021

KCSE, High School Diploma, Musingu Boys

Feb 2014 - Nov 2017

Certificates

Agile Scrum Master(ASM®), Simplilearn

2022-05-01

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing, Google Digital Garage

2020-10-01

Introduction to Git and Github, Coursera

2019-11-01

Interests

web3

Blockchain

Forex

Gaming

Languages

Kiswahili (Native speaker), English (Fluent)

Online Version

Last updated at September 28th 2022, 6:08:54 pm